<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-01-08T13:52:27+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays//</id><title type="html">NYUAD Cyber Mondays</title><subtitle>The cyber security teams in NYU Abu Dhabi get together every Monday, watch security-related videos from top conferences, and discuss! 
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">s02e01 - Gateway to (s)hell</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2018/01/08/s02e01.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s02e01 - Gateway to (s)hell" /><published>2018-01-08T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2018-01-08T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2018/01/08/s02e01</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2018/01/08/s02e01.html">&lt;p&gt;34C3 - SCADA - Gateway to (s)hell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hacking industrial control gateways:&lt;/strong&gt; Small gateways connect all kinds of fieldbusses to IP systems. This talk will look at the (in)security of those gateways, starting with simple vulnerabilities, and then deep diving into reverse-engineering the firmware and breaking the encryption of firmware upgrades. The found vulnerabilities will then be demonstrated live on a portable SCADA system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies often utilize small gateway devices to connect the different field-busses used in industrial control systems (such as Modbus, RS232 etc) to TCP/IP networks. Under the hood, these devices are mostly comprised of ARM-based mini computers, running either custom, tiny operating systems or uClinux/Linux. The talk will look at the security aspects of these gateways by examining known and unfixed vulnerabilities like unchangeable default credentials, protocols that do not support authentication, and reverse engineering and breaking the encryption of firmware upgrades of certain gateways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk will consist of a theoretical part, an introduction on how to reverse-engineer and find vulnerabilities in a firmware-blob of unknown format, and a practical part, showcasing a live ICS environment that utilizes gateways, from both the IP and the field-bus side, to pivot through an industrial control system environment: Demonstrating how to potentially pivot from a station in the field up to the SCADA headquarters, permanently modifying the firmware of the gateways on the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Thomas Roth: Security researcher from Germany, focused on embedded systems and mobile security (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stacksmashing&quot;&gt;@stacksmashing&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Itgwb3rn7gE&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Jan 15, 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">34C3 - SCADA - Gateway to (s)hell</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e11 - The Squirrels are Winning</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/05/02/s01e11.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e11 - The Squirrels are Winning" /><published>2017-05-02T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-05-02T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/05/02/s01e11</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/05/02/s01e11.html">&lt;p&gt;Schmoocon 2017: 35yrs Of Cyberwar, The Squirrels are Winning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WASHINGTON, DC:&lt;/strong&gt; For years, the government and security experts have warned of the looming threat of “cyberwar” against critical infrastructure in the US and elsewhere. Predictions of cyber attacks wreaking havoc on power grids, financial systems, and other fundamental parts of nations’ fabric have been foretold repeatedly over the past two decades, and each round has become more dire. The US Department of Energy declared in its Quadrennial Energy Review, just released this month, that the electrical grid in the US “faces imminent danger from a cyber attack.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, however, the damage done by cyber attacks, both real (Stuxnet’s destruction of Iranian uranium enrichment centrifuges and a few brief power outages alleged to have been caused by Russian hackers using BlackEnergy malware) and imagined or exaggerated (the Iranian “attack” on a broken flood control dam in Rye, New York), cannot begin to measure up to an even more significant cyber-threat—squirrels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the presentation titled “35 Years of Cyberwar: The Squirrels Are Winning”, SpaceRogue revealed the scale of the squirrelly threat to worldwide critical infrastructure by presenting data gathered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cybersquirrel1.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CyberSquirrel 1&lt;/a&gt;, a project that gathers information on animal-induced infrastructure outages collected from sources on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Cris “SpaceRogue” Thomas, former member of the L0pht Heavy Industries hacking collective and now a security researcher at Tenable&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cZPv-wro-O8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: May 08, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Schmoocon 2017: 35yrs Of Cyberwar, The Squirrels are Winning</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e10 - Why we are not building a defendable internet</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/25/s01e10.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e10 - Why we are not building a defendable internet" /><published>2017-04-25T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-04-25T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/25/s01e10</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/25/s01e10.html">&lt;p&gt;Black Hat Asia 2017 Keynote: Why We are Not Building a Defendable Internet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In IT security, offensive problems are technical - but most defensive problems are political and organisational. Attackers have the luxury to focus only on the technical aspects of their work, while defenders have to navigate complex political and regulatory environments. In a previous talk (“Rearchitecting a defendable internet”) I discussed what technical measures would yield defendable devices - and intentionally omitted the political and economics side. This talk, on the other hand, will explore the economics and incentive structures in IT security: Who is incentivized by who to do what - and how these incentives fail to produce the security level we desire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk will look at different players in IT security: CISOs, security product vendors, computer manufacturers, cyber insurances - and examine their economic incentive structures, their interplay, and reasons for failure. The talk will also discuss an alternate reality where things work smoothly, and examine the differences to our current reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Thomas Dullien (aka Halvar Flake): Reverse engineer at Google&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PLJJY5UFtqY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: May 01, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Black Hat Asia 2017 Keynote: Why We are Not Building a Defendable Internet</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e09 - Repsych</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/19/s01e09.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e09 - Repsych" /><published>2017-04-19T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-04-19T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/19/s01e09</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/19/s01e09.html">&lt;p&gt;Repsych: Psychological Warfare in Reverse Engineering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your precious 0-day? That meticulously crafted exploit? The perfect foothold? At some point, they’ll be captured, dissected, and put on display. Reverse engineers. When they begin snooping through your hard work, it pays to have planned out your defense ahead of time. You can take the traditional defensive route - encryption, obfuscation, anti-debugging - or you can go on the offense, and attack the heart and soul of anyone who dare look at your perfect code. With some carefully crafted assembly, we’ll show how to break down a reverse engineer by sending them misleading, intimidating, and demoralizing messages through the control flow graphs of their favorite RE tools - turning their beloved IDA (Hopper, BinNavi, Radare, etc) into unwitting weapons for devastating psychological warfare in reverse engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Chris Domas &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/xoreaxeaxeax&quot;&gt;@xoreaxeaxeax&lt;/a&gt;: Chris is an embedded systems engineer and cyber security researcher, focused on innovative approaches to low level hardware and software RE and exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HlUe0TUHOIc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Apr 24, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Repsych: Psychological Warfare in Reverse Engineering</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e08 - ARMageddon</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/10/s01e08.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e08 - ARMageddon" /><published>2017-04-10T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/10/s01e08</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/04/10/s01e08.html">&lt;p&gt;ARMageddon: How Your Smartphone CPU Breaks Software-Level Security and Privacy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last years, mobile devices and smartphones have become the most important personal computing platform. Besides phone calls and managing the personal address book, they are also used to approve bank transfers and digitally sign official documents, thus storing very sensitive secrets. Their exposure or misappropriation would not only be a fatal infringement of privacy, but could also lead to disastrous consequences in terms of financial security and identity theft. So what if it is possible to silently monitor and track what the user is doing on his smartphone or recovering encryption keys without any permissions or privileges?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this talk, we will show that all of this is possible by mounting cache side-channel attacks on ARM that have been believed to work solely on x86 architecture. We will discuss how we overcame the challenges to perform such attacks on smartphones and demonstrate their immense attack potential. We prepared a live demo to show an unprivileged app that records the exact timestamps of user input activity. We will also present how two apps on a system can communicate with each other, circumventing the permission system and show how we can attack Bouncy Castles AES implementation. We will release source code that allows the user to perform platform-independent attacks within minutes. It serves as a starting point for research on cache side-channel attacks on smartphones and a foundation to build more sophisticated attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Moritz Lipp &amp;amp; Clémentine Maurice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9KsnFWejpQg&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Apr 10, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">ARMageddon: How Your Smartphone CPU Breaks Software-Level Security and Privacy</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e07 - Breaking BHAD</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/14/s01e07.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e07 - Breaking BHAD" /><published>2017-03-14T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-03-14T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/14/s01e07</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/14/s01e07.html">&lt;p&gt;Breaking BHAD: Abusing Belkin Home Automation Devices&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2013 and 2014 several high profile vulnerabilities were found in Belkin’s WeMo line of home automation devices. Belkin not only patched most of those vulnerabilities, but also maintains a very regular update cycle, which makes them one of the more responsive players in the IoT space. Therefore, we thought it would be interesting to revisit this line of IoT products to see how we could break or abuse them. What we found are multiple vulnerabilities in both the device and the Android app that can be used to obtain a root shell on the device, run arbitrary code on the phone paired with the device, deny service to the device, and launch DoS attacks without rooting the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk will walk through the details of heap overflow, SQL injection, and code injection zero days, as well as their associated exploits. We will also introduces a new technique for achieving code execution via SQL injection into a SQLite database on an embedded device. The talk will conclude with demonstrations of rooting a WeMo device and injecting code into the WeMo Android app from a WeMo device. That’s right, we will show you how to make your IoT hack your phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
Scott Tenaglia and Joe Tanen, Invincea Labs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7z56SVUjP0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Mar 27, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Breaking BHAD: Abusing Belkin Home Automation Devices</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e06 - Cryptocurrencies and Beyond</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/07/s01e06.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e06 - Cryptocurrencies and Beyond" /><published>2017-03-07T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-03-07T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/07/s01e06</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/07/s01e06.html">&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies and Beyond&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cryptocurrencies” refer to techniques for purely digital currencies. The most famous of these is Bitcoin, but since its creation numerous other currencies have also been created, relying on the underlying Distributed Ledger Technology to create a publicly verifiable list of transactions: the blockchain. There is considerable interest from the data science community, the financial sector and government in other applications of this technology, and other instantiations of cryptocurrencies that may offer different levels of anonymity, untraceability and verifiability. In this talk IOHK’s chief scientist Aggelos Kiayias presents &lt;a href=&quot;https://eprint.iacr.org/2016/889.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“Secure Decentralized Blockchains without Proofs of Work”&lt;/a&gt; at the Alan Turning Institute in London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kiayias.com/Aggelos_Kiayias/Home_of_Aggelos_Kiayias.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Aggelos Kiayias&lt;/a&gt;, Chief scientist IOHK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professor Aggelos Kiayias is chair in Cyber Security and Privacy at the University of Edinburgh. His research interests are in computer security, information security, applied cryptography and foundations of cryptography with a particular emphasis in blockchain technologies and distributed systems, e-voting and secure multiparty protocols as well as privacy and identity management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=whdUSchadEs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Mar 13, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Cryptocurrencies and Beyond</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e05 - The Internet of Scary Things</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e05 - The Internet of Scary Things" /><published>2017-03-06T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-03-06T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05.html">&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Scary Things - Tips to deploy and manage IoT safely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT has been in the news for the wrong reasons, with poorly designed and managed IoT devices being blamed for contribiting to denial of service attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This presentation covers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Risks to your own business from IoT takeup and how to avoid them&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to be a good citizen by ensuring your devices are not a risk to others&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to run your own IoT control and monitoring hub in the cloud, and to coerce incompatible devices into working together.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Points to consider when selecting IoT products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is immature - many devices are not as secure as they could be.
I cover how to structure your network in order to reduce the attack surface presented by your devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is faceless, many devices are unobtrusive and you may not notice if they “go rogue”. I offer advice on how to establish a management regime to limit the damage a misbehaving device can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is fragmented, everyone is scrabbling to be the market leader, so many products do not work well together. This means each device may want to talk to its own cloud service. I cover how to bridge uncooperative products to narrow or eliminate need for direct internet access, and offer advice on strategies to build a cooperating whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christopher Biggs. Christopher has been into Unix since 1990 and was there at the birth of 386BSD and Linux. He was founding vice president of HUMBUG, the Brisbane open systems user group, and was head of development at a multinational online retailer, stewarding development culture and toolset, and convening a series of lectures and workshops for developers there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his spare time he builds and blogs robots, and adds to the Internet of Things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKJz4aPubNI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Mar 06, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: &lt;a href=&quot;https://krebsonsecurity.com/2017/01/who-is-anna-senpai-the-mirai-worm-author/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Link to Mirai botnet attribution project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">The Internet of Scary Things - Tips to deploy and manage IoT safely</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e04 - Hacking Smart Safes</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e04 - Hacking Smart Safes" /><published>2017-02-23T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-23T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04.html">&lt;p&gt;Hacking Smart Safes - On the Brink of a Robbery&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to crack open a safe full of cash with nothing but a USB stick? Now you can!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Brink’s CompuSafe cash management product line provides a “smart safe as a service” solution to major retailers and fast food franchises. They offer end-to-end management of your cash, transporting it safely from your storefront safe to your bank via armored car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this talk, we’ll uncover a major flaw in the Brink’s CompuSafe and demonstrate how to crack one open in seconds flat. All you need is a USB stick and a large bag to hold all of the cash. We’ll discuss how to remotely takeover the safe with full administrator privileges, and show how to enumerate a target list of other major Brink’s CompuSafe customers (exposed via configuration files stored right on the safe).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At any given time, up to $240,000 can be sitting in each of the 14,000 Brink’s CompuSafe smart safes currently deployed across the United States - potentially billions of dollars just waiting to be stolen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dan “AltF4” Petro and Oscar Salazar, Bishop Fox Security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z8yCiYCNVQQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 27, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Hacking Smart Safes - On the Brink of a Robbery</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e03 - Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless</title><link href="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e03 - Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless" /><published>2017-02-14T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-14T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tkeliris.github.io/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03.html">&lt;p&gt;Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless: A New Front in Cyber Security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;: 
With new Drone technologies appearing in the consumer space daily, Industrial Plant operators are being forced to rethink their most fundamental assumptions about Industrial Wireless and Cyber-Physical security. This presentation will cover Electronic Threats, Electronic Defensive measures, Recent Electronic jamming incidents, Latest Drone Threats and capabilities, defensive planning, and Electronic Attack Threats with Drones as delivery platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Jeff Melrose, Principal Technology Strategist for Cybersecurity at Yokogawa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2URDrYNjKsY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u8qgehH3kEQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Homework&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 20, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless: A New Front in Cyber Security</summary></entry></feed>
