<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-03-06T13:11:31+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays//</id><title type="html">NYUAD Cyber Mondays</title><subtitle>The cyber security teams in NYU Abu Dhabi get together every Monday, watch security-related videos from top conferences, and discuss! 
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">s01e05 - The Internet of Scary Things</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e05 - The Internet of Scary Things" /><published>2017-03-06T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-03-06T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/03/06/s01e05.html">&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Scary Things - Tips to deploy and manage IoT safely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT has been in the news for the wrong reasons, with poorly designed and managed IoT devices being blamed for contribiting to denial of service attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This presentation covers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Risks to your own business from IoT takeup and how to avoid them&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to be a good citizen by ensuring your devices are not a risk to others&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to run your own IoT control and monitoring hub in the cloud, and to coerce incompatible devices into working together.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Points to consider when selecting IoT products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is immature - many devices are not as secure as they could be.
I cover how to structure your network in order to reduce the attack surface presented by your devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is faceless, many devices are unobtrusive and you may not notice if they “go rogue”. I offer advice on how to establish a management regime to limit the damage a misbehaving device can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IoT is fragmented, everyone is scrabbling to be the market leader, so many products do not work well together. This means each device may want to talk to its own cloud service. I cover how to bridge uncooperative products to narrow or eliminate need for direct internet access, and offer advice on strategies to build a cooperating whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christopher Biggs. Christopher has been into Unix since 1990 and was there at the birth of 386BSD and Linux. He was founding vice president of HUMBUG, the Brisbane open systems user group, and was head of development at a multinational online retailer, stewarding development culture and toolset, and convening a series of lectures and workshops for developers there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his spare time he builds and blogs robots, and adds to the Internet of Things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKJz4aPubNI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Mar 06, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">The Internet of Scary Things - Tips to deploy and manage IoT safely</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e04 - Hacking Smart Safes</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e04 - Hacking Smart Safes" /><published>2017-02-23T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-23T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/23/s01e04.html">&lt;p&gt;Hacking Smart Safes - On the Brink of a Robbery&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to crack open a safe full of cash with nothing but a USB stick? Now you can!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Brink’s CompuSafe cash management product line provides a “smart safe as a service” solution to major retailers and fast food franchises. They offer end-to-end management of your cash, transporting it safely from your storefront safe to your bank via armored car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this talk, we’ll uncover a major flaw in the Brink’s CompuSafe and demonstrate how to crack one open in seconds flat. All you need is a USB stick and a large bag to hold all of the cash. We’ll discuss how to remotely takeover the safe with full administrator privileges, and show how to enumerate a target list of other major Brink’s CompuSafe customers (exposed via configuration files stored right on the safe).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At any given time, up to $240,000 can be sitting in each of the 14,000 Brink’s CompuSafe smart safes currently deployed across the United States - potentially billions of dollars just waiting to be stolen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dan “AltF4” Petro and Oscar Salazar, Bishop Fox Security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z8yCiYCNVQQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 27, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Hacking Smart Safes - On the Brink of a Robbery</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e03 - Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e03 - Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless" /><published>2017-02-14T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-14T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/14/s01e03.html">&lt;p&gt;Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless: A New Front in Cyber Security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;: 
With new Drone technologies appearing in the consumer space daily, Industrial Plant operators are being forced to rethink their most fundamental assumptions about Industrial Wireless and Cyber-Physical security. This presentation will cover Electronic Threats, Electronic Defensive measures, Recent Electronic jamming incidents, Latest Drone Threats and capabilities, defensive planning, and Electronic Attack Threats with Drones as delivery platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation by&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Jeff Melrose, Principal Technology Strategist for Cybersecurity at Yokogawa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2URDrYNjKsY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u8qgehH3kEQ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Homework&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 20, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Drone Attacks on Industrial Wireless: A New Front in Cyber Security</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e02 - The NSA Playset: RF Retroreflectors</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/07/s01e02.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e02 - The NSA Playset: RF Retroreflectors" /><published>2017-02-07T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-07T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/07/s01e02</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/07/s01e02.html">&lt;p&gt;Time for some hardware hacking and RF retroreflectors by the creator of the HackRF Software Defined Radio, Michael Ossman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Of all the technologies revealed in the NSA ANT catalog, perhaps the most exotic is the use of RF retroreflectors for over-the-air surveillance. These tiny implants, without any power supply, transmit information intercepted from digital or analog communications when irradiated by radio signals from an outside source. This modern class of radar eavesdropping technology has never been demonstrated in public before today. I’ve constructed and tested my own RF retroreflectors, and I’ll show you how they work and how easy they are to build with modest soldering skills. I’ll even bring along some fully assembled units to give away. Now you can add RF retroreflectors to your own NSA Playset and play along with the NSA!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bio&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Michael Ossmann is a wireless security researcher who makes hardware for hackers. Best known for the open source HackRF, Ubertooth, and Daisho projects, he founded Great Scott Gadgets in an effort to put exciting, new tools into the hands of innovative people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mAai6dRAtFo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 13, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Time for some hardware hacking and RF retroreflectors by the creator of the HackRF Software Defined Radio, Michael Ossman.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e01 - Pwned By The Owner</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/06/s01e01.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e01 - Pwned By The Owner" /><published>2017-02-06T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2017-02-06T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/06/s01e01</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2017/02/06/s01e01.html">&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&quot;/cybermondays/2016/12/20/Pilot.html&quot;&gt;Pilot&lt;/a&gt; post I introduced the concept of CyberMondays for NYUAD. Now it’s time to make it a reality. I feel it is appropriate that the first video is by good-ol-fashioned Zoz. For Monday Feb. 06, 2017 we’ll watch a DEFCON video and see what happens when you steal a hacker’s computer (funny things happen)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this first week I’ll try the afternoon thing (17:00-18:00) and see how it goes. I’ll bring the popcorn :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jwpg-AwJ0Jc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube link to presentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;air date: Feb 06, 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">In the Pilot post I introduced the concept of CyberMondays for NYUAD. Now it’s time to make it a reality. I feel it is appropriate that the first video is by good-ol-fashioned Zoz. For Monday Feb. 06, 2017 we’ll watch a DEFCON video and see what happens when you steal a hacker’s computer (funny things happen)!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">s01e00 - Pilot</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2016/12/20/Pilot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="s01e00 - Pilot" /><published>2016-12-20T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2016-12-20T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2016/12/20/Pilot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cybermondays/2016/12/20/Pilot.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while that I’ve been entertaining the idea of establishing an event for the cyber security folks here at NYU Abu Dhabi. So… The idea goes more or less like this: Every (Cyber)Monday we get together in the Twinlab conference room (comfy couches) and watch a video presentation from a top security conference (DEFCON, BlackHat, CCS,  etc.) and then chat about it! I’m not yet sure about the time to do this, I was thinking it could be over lunch (12:15-13:15) or in the afternoon (17:00-18:00). I would love your feedback on it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you liked what you read subscribe to the RSS feed or bookmark this page and be on the lookout for another post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8qnQz8kxte0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Homework&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Tasos&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">It’s been a while that I’ve been entertaining the idea of establishing an event for the cyber security folks here at NYU Abu Dhabi. So… The idea goes more or less like this: Every (Cyber)Monday we get together in the Twinlab conference room (comfy couches) and watch a video presentation from a top security conference (DEFCON, BlackHat, CCS,  etc.) and then chat about it! I’m not yet sure about the time to do this, I was thinking it could be over lunch (12:15-13:15) or in the afternoon (17:00-18:00). I would love your feedback on it!</summary></entry></feed>
